Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ Do we know where the light
is the brightest? ♪
♪ Do we know how to clear
what the fear is? ♪
♪ Do we know how to feel
when we crave it? ♪
♪ Do we know what we are? ♪
Every family is weird.
But trust me,
mine is the weirdest.
My mom is pretty normal,
but my dad...
is Bigfoot.
Yes. The Bigfoot.
I don't look it
but I'm a Bigfoot too.
I got all of the magical powers,
but luckily none of the fur.
What powers?
Like the name Bigfoot implies,
I've got big feet.
They were annoying at first.
I went through a lot shoes.
But barefoot, these babies can move.
Wow.
Hi...
Yes, I am with Adam.
I got great hearing.
Yeah, he is so cute.
But he's very shy.
What?
Sometimes embarrassingly so.
Also, Bigfoots have the power to heal.
It's handy for all injuries.
We save a ton on medical bills.
And there's one more thing,
I can talk to animals.
Morning Adam.
Hey Wilbur.
Don't use up the hot water.
Uh-uh. Not my fault.
Look at me,
I've got a lot of surface area.
We live with animals.
They were friends with my dad
in the forest.
Now they're family.
We're making pancakes,
you hungry?
- Hit me.
- Here.
Go for it.
Woah... Oh.
- Thanks.
- Nice catch.
My pleasure.
Morning everyone.
Adam, clean your bathroom.
There's so much hair.
- Not mine.
- Have a pancake.
Oh, shoot.
Uh, Trapper, what did I say
about throwing food?
Come on, that was a great toss.
Your fault you can't catch.
Having said that...
What'd he say?
My mom can't talk to animals,
so it's up to me keep the peace.
Trapper says he is so sorry,
and you look lovely this morning.
I didn't say that.
Don't misrepresent me.
Like I said: my family is the weirdest.
You know,
for such a big fella,
you sure drink a tiny cup of coffee.
Any more,
and I won't hibernate for a year.
Personally, I need a bit more
of a kick in the morning.
Oh. It's almost time.
Where's the remote?
I'm on it.
We're taking care of the environment.
Clean oil by X-TRAKT.
You're watching Good Morning World.
I'm Becky Dabmore.
My next guest needs no introduction,
but I'll introduce him anyway.
He's come out
of the woodwork, literally.
And here he is, the man
everyone's talking about...
Bigfoot.
Ooh. I'm loving the new look.
It's an upgrade over the jean shorts.
Thanks Becky.
There weren't fancy clothing shops
when I was hiding in the forest.
So, I've got to start with the question
that is on everyone's mind.
Where have you been all these years?
Well, it's a complicated story.
I was a scientist
studying genetic sequencing,
when an experiment went wrong.
My DNA mutated
and turned me into Bigfoot.
I think we can all agree, oof,
you make those mutations
look good. Ugh.
Am I right ladies?
Yes.
Now where were we?
I hid when I was being hunted
by a pharmaceutical company.
They wanted to take me
and study my genetic mutation.
But when they were brought down,
I could come live with my family again.
That must have been a shock for them.
I owe it all to my son, Adam.
He tracked me down
and brought me home.
Oh, I hate that picture.
I can see why.
But don't feel bad.
Not everyone's as photogenic as me.
Look at my face,
I don't have a bad side.
Shh. Stop talking.
It's amazing to finally be back home.
And better
if you were ever here.
Oh come on, be supportive.
Even though you're not climbing
trees all day,
ooh, you are still in incredible shape.
Getting a little handsy there, Becky.
- Your muscles are so big.
- Ugh.
You're in such incredible shape.
Bleh.
- Where's your support?
- Don't use my words against me.
So, you're a big star now.
I am not so sure about that.
Oh, come on.
We all want a piece of those big feet.
What's next?
Clothing line? Sneaker endorsement?
Video game deal?
I should introduce you
to my agent.
You know, I just want to find a way
to make the world better.
Aww. That is so sweet.
Ladies and gentlemen, Bigfoot.
That was a lovely interview.
Bigfoot came off like such a gentleman.
I thought he looked puffy.
Did they blow dry his fur?
This is why I think
he needs a full time road manager.
Oh, let me guess,
you want the job?
Naturally. I've got an eye for show biz.
The glitz, the glamor.
Maybe he should get a road manager
who doesn't have fleas.
Hey!
My fleas have more integrity
than half the people in this business.
Alright, time's up. You've got school.
Yeah, great.
Adam! Can your dad sign my poster?
Can Bigfoot come to my birthday party?
But just him, to keep it small.
Your dad is like super duper cool.
Can you him give my letter?
Children, disperse from this hallway
immediately!
You're violating fire code.
Adam, you and I go way back.
We understand each other.
You suspended me two months ago.
Oh, Adam.
That was just
an administrative error.
But you're the administrator.
Be that as it may,
could you do me a solid
and get your dad to sign this picture?
- Make it out to "Principal Jones".
- Hold on.
- No...
- Not now.
"My good friend Principal Jones".
Better yet, "My best friend,
Principal Barenthal Jones".
- Hey.
- Ah.
Ahh.
With nice big letters,
so I can frame it!
Oh!
Make it out to Steven!
Can your dad sign it...
Make it to Lucy.
Come on, please Adam...
- Make my day.
- Come on.
That is so funny.
Emma?
See you.
Ah!
Ow.
Oh, great.
Adam?
- What are you doing in there?
- Oh... Uh.
Just doing research for my paper
on trash recycling.
Really? I didn't realize dumpster diving
was your thing.
Oh yeah.
I'm a big time dumpster diver.
So, this is a pretty crazy time for you.
I just wanted my dad back.
But now he's so busy,
it's like he isn't back.
It's weird how life seems
to be going great,
then it throws you a curve ball.
Yeah, tell me about it.
I assumed my parents
would be together forever,
but that sure didn't happen.
Maybe we shouldn't expect much
from others.
I just thought things
would finally be normal.
But they're not.
Now he's famous,
everybody wants something from him.
Look on the bright side,
people love your dad.
He makes them happy.
Sometimes, I wish he was still a secret.
What is that?
We needed a bigger ride
when we added a bear to the family.
You're going to take your driver's test
in that thing?
- I didn't even think about that.
- Good luck parallel parking.
That's a guaranteed fail.
I'll be taking the bus forever.
Taking the bus?
You're driving the bus.
Ding! This is your stop.
See you later.
Hey Emma, I was thinking...
we could go to the movies sometime.
Like on a date or whatever.
Argh. I'm pathetic.
Forget third world,
I want fourth world prices.
Hold off until I see the contract.
What? No, he can't fax it over.
It's not 1983. Fax is dead.
How you doing kid?
Here you go, on the house.
Wait, scratch that.
The manufacturer's cost.
Oh, wait a minute,
wholesaler's cost. Okay?
What? No, I told you...
Want some of this?
Eat that you identical looking bad guys.
Boom, fireball! Ooo.
Wait, Bigfoot shoots fireballs?
This game's logic strains credulity.
What's going on?
Where'd he come from?
This Bigfoot game stinks.
The raccoon's the weakest character
and has no special moves.
Armor, zero.
Magic, zero. Strength, zero.
This is shameful.
- Hey, how was your day?
- You don't want to know.
What's all this?
This stuff showed up
after the TV appearance.
Who's that guy?
He came with the junk.
Well, I think you look handsome.
Not on this one.
Yikes.
Bigfoot, you've gotta pull the trigger
and sign these contracts now.
Strike while the iron's hot,
because you're only hot
until you're not.
Sheesh,
this guy is all about the hard sell.
Don't let him rush you.
Don't sign until they agree
to a line of plush toys based on me.
Those would sell like hotcakes.
We'll do variants
to shaft the collectors.
We can do "cute and cuddly",
"fierce and fangy".
Maybe one of me in repose?
Oh, I don't want this.
Why, the money's not good enough?
You drive a hard bargain Bigfoot,
but I respect that.
But we'll get you more.
We'll up your percentage.
I mean I don't want to do this.
Period.
No "licensing my likeness
in all media and methods
of dissemination". Bla bla bla.
What?
I got to deal with something.
I'll call you back.
I don't want to sell junk
with my face on it.
I want to do something meaningful.
Meaningful?
I can't take ten percent of meaningful.
And this letter from the non-profit?
Do you have any idea
why they call it a non-profit?
Hey.
Because they don't make any profit!
Take your junk and get out.
These things happen.
I get tempers are hot.
So, just sleep on it.
I can't stand that guy.
This is getting out of hand.
You didn't take the money.
What's your deal?
Three people and ten animals
live in this small house.
You can always sleep
outside in the rain.
Who me? No way, I love it here.
Thanks guys.
"Dear Doctor Harrison..."
Woops.
"We're writing to you from Alaska.
The government's authorized X-TRAKT
to remove oil
from our largest wildlife preserve.
This is because X-TRAKT
convinced the government
that their 'clean oil' process
has zero environmental impact.
We think X-TRAKT is lying,
and they're jeopardizing the ecosystem.
With your fame,
you could expose what's going on here,
and stop it before it's too late.
Signed: Pam and Shamus."
X-TRAKT. These guys are everywhere.
- Do you believe in destiny?
- Here we go again.
This is what I was meant to do.
Use my voice to help people.
I think I should go.
To Alaska? Seriously?
I can make a difference there.
No way. You just got home,
you can't leave again.
What's the point of fame
if I don't make the world better?
You know what?
I hate to break it to you,
but one person
can't make a difference
all by themselves.
You're wrong. Let me prove it.
And what about me?
We need to talk this over.
For the record,
I would have taken the money.
Adam? Can we talk?
About what?
You're home after all these years
and already want to leave.
Have a fun vacation.
You know it's not like that.
I need to do something with my life.
And I need sleep.
I got school tomorrow.
I love you, buddy.
♪ I'm moving on ♪
♪ Something new is coming ♪
♪ Flying high ♪
♪ Above it all ♪
♪ Know it's the right way... ♪
You okay back there?
Fine. Just never been
in such a little plane before.
It's bumpy.
This, this is nothing.
It's cloudy. I was hoping
to get some good shots from up here.
A filmmaker? Why didn't you say so?
I like action movies. Here we go.
Ah! What are you, a stunt pilot?
Ahh!
♪ Moving on ♪
♪ Something new is coming ♪
♪ Flying high ♪
♪ Above it all ♪
I'm not a flier. More of a land mammal.
Go on, take it, you're missing the shot.
Oh, hey, look over here.
This is always a cool angle.
Boring shots,
I want more boring shots.
♪ Ooo ♪
You got all the shots you need?
I could whip you 'round again.
Show you the old loop de loop.
Come on.
No thanks.
I think I got it.
Alright, take it easy.
Wow.
♪ I wanna get lost ♪
♪ With you on a mountain top ♪
♪ Get lost, with you ♪
Oh right there. Okay.
Bigfoot here. I just landed
in Rocky Valley, Alaska.
I'm here to do what I can
to save this place.
But first thing's first,
I gotta find those who invited me.
Look at this place.
The air is so fresh and clean.
And listen to how quiet it is...
Yippie!
We'll have to cut that part out.
Back in the day,
Rocky Valley used to be a mining town.
This old ghost town has been deserted
for over a century.
It's good to see
that nature is reclaiming the land.
They call it a ghost town,
but we all know
there's no such thing as ghosts.
Well, that's creepy.
Hello, is someone there?
Okay. There, like that.
Oof.
You got my heart racing there.
- I thought you might be a ghost.
- Hey, get off my land!
What?
- Buzz off.
- What?
Woah!
- Hold on there. Stop.
- You get what that means?
- It means get off my land...
- Woah.
Ah!
We'll have to edit that out.
Hey ho. Hey ho.
X-TRAKT Oil has got to go.
Hi there.
Wow, look who's here.
Dr. Harrison, hi.
I'm Pam, we talked on the phone.
Nice to meet you.
Call me Bigfoot, everyone does.
I'm Shamus.
Thank you so much for coming.
You've got a cause
worth fighting for.
I couldn't wait to get here.
That said, I expected,
well... more people.
So far, there's only the two of us.
But we're highly motivated.
Well, it's a start.
So, where's the oil company?
Somewhere on the other side
of that bridge.
Nobody can get close.
They got guards patrolling
and drones blocking the airspace.
Nothing shady going on there.
Well I'm here to help amplify
your message.
Hey man, I'm Arlo.
Welcome to Rocky Valley.
Arlo grew up in Alaska,
so our cause is close to his heart.
We're camped out over there.
Find yourself a patch of earth,
and throw down your gear.
Thanks, I will.
But first, jump over there with the...
the rest of the group.
To anybody out there watching,
this is a call to action.
Write to your local representative,
share this video,
or if you're up for an adventure,
come join us in Alaska
and make your voice heard.
Remember that whoever you are,
wherever you are,
you can make a difference.
Not gonna make a difference
with 14 views.
14 views.
- I'd get more with the lens cap on.
- I feel sorry for him.
At that rate, he's not gonna be home
for Christmas. He needs our help.
I thought one man
could make a difference.
- Come on, be a good sport.
- Okay. Okay.
We can spice it up.
Let's add music and snappy editing.
Drag, drop, throw in the trims bin.
Gimme one of them star wipes.
No star wipes.
What do you mean no star wipes?
This must look professional.
To anybody out there,
this is a call to action.
To action.
The government
just authorized X-TRAKT
to remove oil from our wildlife reserve.
Share this video,
or if you're up for an adventure,
come join us in Alaska.
- Alaska, Alaska.
- Oh yeah.
Remember that whoever you are,
wherever you are,
you can make a difference.
- Much better.
- You're no Spielberg, but it'll do.
- Hey, Emma.
- Hey,
- how are you doing?
- Great, I wanna ask you something.
Oh, tell me?
My dad's internet game is super weak,
and he needs all the help he can get.
I edited his video, and was wondering
if your soccer team could share it?
- Yeah. Uh, I'll text them right now.
- Thanks.
- You rock.
- Yep.
Hopefully this gets
enough attention for you to come home.
That's enough, this is my internet time.
Ooo. That's the good stuff right there.
Ugh, I can't believe
you look at that trash.
One man's trash
is another man's treasure.
♪ Light speed ♪
Oh.
- Who are all these people?
- Your video went viral, man.
They're coming in from all over.
It gave your computer a virus?
No man, the video went viral.
Like everybody's seen it.
Oh, that's good then.
- Heck yes, it's good.
- Yeah, way to go, Bigfoot.
Put on some sandals, throw on a poncho,
and we'll get you some kombucha
and goji berry granola.
I have no idea what that is,
but I'm starving.
The abandoned mining town
has come into the spotlight
as a small group of protesters take on
- the oil giant X-TRAKT...
- Dad's message is spreading.
Rocky Valley is on the news.
The new face of the protesters?
Bigfoot.
One accident could destroy
Rocky Valley's fragile ecosystem,
and that's why we're up here.
To show people what's at stake,
and to push back against the oil company
putting all this at risk.
Why you?
Why is Bigfoot the face of this protest?
I'm getting my 15 minutes of fame,
and I'm not gonna waste it.
If we bring enough public pressure
against X-TRAKT,
they'll have to shut this down.
We've got Connor Mandrake,
the new CEO of the X-TRAKT oil company,
which has been run by his family
for 3 generations.
Thanks, it's great to be on the show.
I have a question.
How'd you get to work today?
- I drove.
- Exactly.
The world still needs oil.
Back in my father's day,
extracting oil made a heck of a mess.
That's what drove us to invent
X-TRAKT's new Clean Oil technology.
We're more of a tech company now.
Our operation at Rocky Valley
has zero environmental footprint.
I want to assure all the protesters
that X-TRAKT oil has evolved
with the times.
Nobody cares more about the environment
than me.
Thanks informing our viewers
about X-TRAKT's vision for clean oil.
We'll be right back
after these messages.
Clean oil? You gotta be kidding.
That was like an ad for the oil company.
Taking ad money from your guests?
So much for journalistic integrity.
Hey, look at the ad.
X-TRAKT puts nature first.
Just look around.
We're taking care
of the environment.
Clean oil by X-TRAKT.
For a cleaner tomorrow.
I love that jingle.
Makes me want buy some oil.
Ugh, are you kidding me?
♪ X-TRAKT got us down ♪
♪ But we pushed back ♪
♪ Cause Bigfoot came to town, mhm ♪
♪ Bigfoot came to town, uh-huh ♪
♪ Bigfoot came ♪
♪ To town... ♪
Hey. What's going on, bro?
X-TRAKT says their clean oil
has zero environmental footprint.
If they say it enough,
people will believe it.
Oh. Fake news, man. It's a new era.
Our word against theirs.
Why the armed guards, drones,
and electric fences
if all is A-Okay?
They say they wanna keep their clean oil
extraction process secret,
at least until it's patented.
We have to find out
what's across that bridge.
If their process is as clean
as they claim,
they should show us.
But if it's not, and they're lying,
we can shut X-TRAKT down for good.
Woah. That's deep, man.
♪ When Bigfoot came to town,
yeah baby ♪
♪ Bigfoot came to town,
I'm telling you ♪
♪ Bigfoot came to town ♪
♪ Cause Bigfoot came to town, mhm ♪
♪ Bigfoot came to town, uh-huh ♪
Nah, it's too far away.
♪ Let's go running around
while we can ♪
♪ Anywhere we wanna go ♪
♪ Take your time,
we must plan for the sky ♪
♪ To fall down ♪
♪ On the other side of town ♪
♪ Let's go running around while we can ♪
♪ Any way we wanna go,
take your time ♪
♪ We must plan for the sky
to fall down ♪
♪ On the other side of town ♪
I knew they were lying,
look at that.
Hey... Woah.
You're not getting rid of me that easy.
Mm. Okay, I'm up.
Let's see how many views
you got last night.
Ugh, Dad, what did you do?
You've reached Dr. Harrison,
also known as Bigfoot,
please leave a message.
Hey Dad, it's me.
You deleted all your videos,
and your password no longer works.
Call me back, and I'll talk you through
how to fix it. Okay, bye.
The verdict's in.
Dad has no idea how to use his computer.
If you look like a caveman,
your computer skills...
Shh.
...as Bigfoot,
leader of oil drilling protesters...
- is missing.
- What?
Well I saw him leave
his tent last night.
I assumed it was just like
a bathroom trip to the woods.
I didn't offer to go with him
because that would be strange.
X-TRAKT guys said their security cameras
showed him crossing the bridge.
They went to look for him,
but this is all that was left.
Apparently, it was
a pretty gruesome scene.
Looks like Bigfoot was attacked
by wolves.
- Attacked by wolves?
- Makes no sense.
Dad talks to animals,
they'd leave him be.
Adam's right, this makes no sense.
That's just impossible.
Something weird's going on.
Maybe the call of the wild was strong,
and he's leaving us.
No, not a chance.
Adam, he was really happy
to be back home.
We need to catch
the next flight to Alaska.
Forget flying.
If we're going out to the woods,
we need Wilbur as backup.
Let's take the camper.
I'm right here,
and you know I want to go.
Fine. Wilbur and Trapper.
Woah, woah. Hold on,
you want us to drive miles
in that musty old camper
with a grizzly bear and a raccoon?
I'm not saying it's gonna smell great.
But we'll do it for Dad.
Alright, we're packed.
♪ Let's get out of town ♪
Bye, girls. Take care of your mom.
Don't do anything stupid, honey.
- I can't make any promises.
- Hey, Steve...
Make sure you tape my shows!
I'll even wait to watch them
with you.
Huh, I ain't waiting.
I'm watching.
What? I gotta know if Brandine wakes up
from her coma
and meets her long lost twin sister.
- I've just got to know.
- Wah.
Woah.
Ow.
I'll be gone for a bit.
Can you grab my homework?
Thanks. Okay, gotta go.
No, you hang up first.
- No, you.
- Let me help you.
Hey!
Oh la la.
Was that your girlfriend?
Shut up,
or you're going on the roof.
I apologize. My mouth got ahead of me.
- I get rowdy when I travel.
- Buckle up.
My seat belt won't fit.
Seat belts aren't for animals.
We don't play by human rules.
Watch out.
I guess they got those seat belt rules
for a reason.
Better play it safe.
Your mom's a reckless driver.
- What did he say?
- Uh...
He likes your musical taste.
Yeah, really. That's what he said?
Huh?
♪ Don't sit down, turn around ♪
♪ And let's get out of this town ♪
♪ Where the people have scars ♪
♪ Just from livin' ♪
♪ And let's drive on down below
on this solemn country road ♪
♪ While city lights fade fast
in the night ♪
♪ Searching high, searching low ♪
♪ We don't know yet where to go ♪
♪ But our faces are pointing ♪
♪ To the target ♪
♪ No matter what we left behind ♪
♪ We'll keep moving till we find ♪
♪ Another place without a name
and not a sign ♪
♪ Let's get lost in the open
just to find ♪
♪ Our lost ♪
♪ Peace of mind ♪
♪ Let's go out ♪
♪ Find a heaven in the world ♪
♪ To claim ♪
♪ Our peace of mind ♪
♪ Out in the open ♪
♪ Ohhh ♪
♪ Let's get lost in the open
just to find ♪
♪ Our lost ♪
♪ Our peace of mind... ♪
♪ Out in the open ♪
Who are you texting?
Nobody.
- Is it Emma?
- Maybe.
She's such a nice girl, and very pretty.
- Have you told her you like her?
- Mom. Please.
Your father was the same way at first.
Too shy to tell me.
I'm gonna jump out the window
if you don't stop talking.
You know,
I'll never forget our first kiss.
- It was...
- La la la, I can't hear you.
Seesh. He cuts her off just when
the story was starting to get good.
I hope Dad is okay.
He spent over 10 years
in the wilderness.
I am sure he's fine.
He may miss his old life style.
We may never see him again.
You want him gone?
♪ Let's get lost in the river
just to find ♪
♪ Our lost ♪
♪ Peace of mind ♪
♪ Let's go out ♪
♪ Find a heaven in the world ♪
♪ To claim ♪
♪ Our peace of mind ♪
♪ Out in the open ♪
Here we are!
Home of the Rocky Valley Mine.
Call the Public Works Committee.
My first ghost town.
Ohh. I'm scared.
There's no ghosts,
it's just the name.
No, I'm scared I won't be able to get
a good thin crust pizza out here.
We're stuck.
- Can you back out?
- No, we're just spinning.
If we die out here,
we'd be the ghosts in this ghost town.
Trapper.
What?
Ah, give me a break.
We're a thousand miles from a tow truck.
Ugh, I wish dad were here.
Thanks for the ringing endorsement,
glad I could help.
Sorry,
that's not what I meant.
Sorry, you scared us.
Me? I don't think I've ever scared
anyone before.
I guess we're all just a little jumpy.
You gotta warn somebody
when you got a grizzly
- in the back of your camper van.
- That's Wilbur. He's harmless.
You're one of the protesters.
We saw you on TV.
Hey, the name's Arlo. Arlo Woodstock.
Hi, Arlo. I'm looking for my husband,
James Harrison.
He's 6'1", brown eyes, great smile...
He's also Bigfoot. In the future,
you should probably lead with that.
Yes, he's Bigfoot.
I'm still not used to calling him that.
So, where are the other protesters?
After what happened to Bigfoot,
they got scared and bugged out.
They're lying
about what happened to him.
He's tough,
he can handle himself in the wild.
Not sure it'll help you,
but I can take you where I last saw him.
I'm going with Arlo.
Adam, stay here with Wilbur.
No way. I didn't come to Alaska
just to wait in the car.
Let me make sure it's safe,
then I'll come back for you.
Listen to your mom, kid.
You'll be safer here with the bear.
Uh, I think.
- Mom.
- Adam, this is not up for debate.
Lock the door, and only open it for me.
Okay.
You let anything happen to him,
you're a rug.
- A rug? Ooo.
- Ow.
Oh, yes, ma'am.
Paper, scissors, stone.
I win.
No, I win.
Stone over scissor.
What scissor?
This is a clean sheet of paper.
Oh, you cheater.
Okay, okay, okay.
- How about a game of poker?
- Okay.
Sorry Wilbur, 4 two's, I win.
Uh, are you sure?
Of course I am sure.
A two is better than a one.
Oh, you cheater.
I was a millionaire on paper,
but the market tanked
before I sold my shares.
- Unbelievable.
- It's been too long.
- I'm gonna check it out.
- Uh-uh.
Can't let you go, I promised your mom.
Given our past,
you side with her over me?
Absolutely. I'm terrified of your mom.
She might turn me into a rug.
Me too, she's got
that crazy look in her eyes.
- Total psycho.
- Shh.
There's a noise. Get down.
- Who is it?
- Your mom's friend. Open up.
Her friend?
She doesn't know anybody here.
Sure she does. She told me
to come get you. Hurry up, we gotta go.
Ugh, we ain't got time for this.
Woah.
Ahh.
Oh, oh boy.
Show's over.
You're coming with us.
- Woah.
- Adam.
Get him.
Run! Get out of here.
Ahh. Ow.
Ow.
Go, go. Nail him.
Woah.
What the...?
Alright, over here.
You're gonna get it.
Ahh.
He is running away.
Come on, let's go.
Ah.
Oh!
Ahh!
Woah, he jumped.
There's no way he survived that.
We're done here.
Ah!
That figures, no signal.
Ahh!
Get off me.
Humans don't belong here.
- Go home.
- Ah.
I'm here to find my dad.
You... you can understand me?
Yes, I can talk to animals.
I'm not here to hurt you, trust me.
Ah... Ow.
No human is to be trusted.
You destroy our land
and poison the ground we walk on.
All you care about
is the black smelly water.
That's not true.
My dad came here
to stop the oil company,
but then he disappeared.
Maybe you're going to disappear too.
Not all humans are bad.
If you help me find my dad,
I promise we'll protect your valley.
Why should I believe you?
Either I'm being honest,
and we can help each other,
or I'm lying and you can eat me.
Hmm.
Not much meat on those bones.
Well, it's what I've got to offer.
Plus, I don't plan on getting eaten.
I'm telling the truth.
I don't know where your father is.
But I can show you
where to start looking.
Huh?
Ouch.
Come on, big galoot, get up.
You can't handle one lousy dart?
Oh. That'd do it.
Ugh.
Alright, we're stranded out here
and we're all on our own.
We gotta take stock of our supplies.
Oh.
Phew. Okay big guy,
I know you like to eat,
but we need to ration our food.
♪ Hallelujah ♪
Of course, we don't wanna get so weak
that we're defenseless.
And you're out cold.
I gotta keep my strength up.
This is to protect you.
I won't enjoy
this double fudge caramel wafer.
Oh man that's good.
It also brings me...
no joy to eat this entire...
bag of marshmallows.
Mmm. Oh, that's good.
Keep up. Not much further now.
You said that two hours ago.
Ugh. I'm dying for something to eat.
And I'd like to eat something
that's dying.
Good one.
Play on words.
Hey, where are you going?
- Huh?
- Oh. Wolf. Run!
Woah, stop. What are you doing?
- What's your deal?
- You know this maniac?
- Are you two in cahoots?
- It's not like that.
I get how this works.
You lure me out, he eats me!
- Go on, I'll stop him.
- Don't put me down, are you nuts?
- No.
- Stop.
I said stop.
Woah... Oof.
What is wrong with you?
Ah, it's instinct,
I couldn't help myself.
If you were a vegetarian,
it would be a lot easier
for you to make friends... Oh.
Does the phrase "lone wolf" ring a bell?
I'm not here to make friends.
Now come on, it's just over that ridge.
Okay... let's go.
Ah!
Jeez.
So much for clean oil,
leaving no impact.
Get down.
Robot bird.
I'll bet you my dad's down there.
Let's go.
- Come on.
- This is far as I go.
What?
I will not walk on poisoned land.
Uh, you're just gonna leave me?
I kept my promise by bringing you here.
Now you keep yours, and save our valley.
Hmm.
As soon as we finish in Alaska,
we'd be delighted
to bring our clean oil process
to your town.
Yes, yes, that sounds perfect.
Man I hate drilling in Alaska,
it's way too cold.
I hear ya.
I wish we were still drilling in Texas.
Nah, I hate Texas, too.
It's way too hot.
You're difficult to please, Roy.
X-TRAKT puts nature first.
Just look around,
we're taking care of the environment.
Clean oil by X-TRAKT,
for a cleaner tomorrow.
Ah.
Perfect. We'll talk to you soon.
Bye now.
Can you believe that?
Clean oil extraction.
Everybody is so gullible.
Ain't that right, Grandpa?
We Mandrakes can sell snow to an eskimo.
All you gotta do is look the part.
First you got your sparkly ring.
And your 10 gallon Stetson.
Let's not forget
the old big belt buckle.
That's it.
Pew, pew.
Ah, looking good.
Yes?
What? Give me one minute.
I'm on my way.
Dang it, what's the holdup?
Mr. Mandrake,
drilling through the frozen ground
is taking longer than we anticipated.
You eggheads didn't think
Alaska would be cold?
We have our IPO at the end of the month,
and I need results now.
But sir, there's also been
some concern raised
about the BD-416 impact charge.
The BD-416? That's a terrible name.
Doesn't have a ring to it.
From now on we call that bomb...
the "Big Daddy".
Yes sir. So, the bad news is:
The shockwave from the "Big...
The "Big Daddy"
that will fracture the bedrock,
and will force a lot of oil
to the surface.
The level will be higher
than anticipated,
flooding the entire valley.
Cool! Maximum impact for maximum oil.
That's not bad news.
What about
the larger environmental impact?
Pfft. With Bigfoot
and his hippie followers gone,
who's watching?
But of course, with heavy hearts,
we'll issue the standard apology.
Wow.
Psst. Hey, kid. Down here.
Arlo?
Dude, don't go that way,
there's guards waiting for you up there.
There's another way out.
Follow me. Hurry.
- What are you doing here?
- Uh, your mom.
She sent me to get you.
She's worried sick dude.
- Is she okay?
- She's fine, man.
Hold this for a second, will you?
Yeah and let's make it nice
and tight and comfortable for you.
What are you doing?
You hippies are so trusting,
it's pathetic.
It's why we always bring you down
from the inside, punk.
- I thought you were one of us.
- Sorry to burst your bubble, kid,
dude, yeah whatever.
I'm a hired gun.
I follow the money,
and there's always money in big oil.
Tell the boss I'm coming in
with the intruder.
Don't even try it, kid.
Ugh.
What happened?
Ohh.
Those X-TRAKT goons shot us with darts,
put us in the trailer,
and then into a ditch.
You know what's worse?
They took all our food.
Every single last piece.
Mmm.
Then they came back
and left us the trash.
That's terrible.
Where's Adam?
He and his big feet
out-ran them.
We've gotta go after him.
How can we do that?
We're stuck in a ditch.
It's okay.
I'll push.
You think you can drive this thing?
Yeah, what kind of questions is that?
I'm a raccoon.
Of course I can drive this thing.
Ugh.
Thanks for the help.
Yeah.
Get off my land.
Get out of here.
Buzz off.
Grr.
- Wait.
- Get off my land.
Wait.
Hold on.
- Bailed out by a moose.
- Woah.
That won't look good on your resume.
Come on lazy bones, quit sitting around.
We gotta find Adam.
Move over NASCAR,
there's a new champ in town.
Ahh.
Woah!
Out of the way, knuckleheads!
I only got one rock,
and it lives on the gas pedal.
You're doing great,
you're a natural.
We have a perimeter breach
on the bridge. Woah.
I repeat,
a perimeter breach.
They're in a camper van.
Woah, woah. Did you say camper van?
Hey Wilbur,
can you read English?
- No, why?
- There's a bunch of signs flying by.
Probably just ads.
Too bad, suckers, I can't read.
You ain't getting my money.
In case this is it,
I gotta tell you something.
I love you too, Trapper.
Not that.
You know how I told you
the X-TRAKT guys took all our food?
- Yeah.
- Well, I... Ahh!
- You okay?
- Uh...
What were you going to say about
those X-TRAKT guys taking our food?
Uh. I was gonna say...
It's just so unfair.
How could they?
That's all.
Grr.
You know, you're trespassing.
- I could have you arrested.
- Great idea.
Let's call the cops.
Up here, we prefer
to handle security ourselves.
Is it worth destroying
this place for oil?
Absolutely.
You think I give a hoot
about this "high tech" clean energy?
Not a chance. I'm an oil man.
My daddy was an oil man,
my daddy's daddy was an oil man.
Oil's not going away on my watch.
With this new extraction method,
oil's about
to get a lot more profitable.
What did you do with my parents?
Tell you what, I'm make you a deal.
If you don't tell anyone what you saw,
I'll take you to them.
Whatever it takes,
I just want my family back.
Wise choice.
After all,
family is the most important thing.
Well then, allow me to reunite you.
They're down there somewhere.
Break, you piece of junk.
This is Adam Harrison.
I'm underground with no signal.
This phone has enough evidence on it
to bring down X-TRAKT.
Whoever finds this,
post these videos
and expose these people
for who they really are.
Mom and Dad, if you see this,
there's some stuff I wanna say.
Dad, I'm sorry for getting mad at you
for coming to Alaska.
You were right,
this place is worth saving.
And Mom, I love you and I want you know
how much I appreciate everything.
Well, except your meatloaf.
And finally, Emma.
It turns out, life is short.
I wish I would've told you
how I felt.
To be honest,
I'm going to miss you so much.
Grr.
Woah.
Ahh.
Mom, look! It's me.
Adam! I've been so worried about you.
Are you okay?
Easy Mom, it hurts.
Let me get those off you.
Woah, woah.
Careful with that thing.
Stay still.
Thanks. Have you seen dad?
He's got to be down here too.
The tunnels go on forever.
I don't know how to find him.
Dad's got great hearing.
If we make enough noise, he'll hear us.
- Dad!
- Jim!
Ahh.
Dad?
It's him. I can hear him.
Are you sure?
Yeah,
it's coming from this way.
Ahh.
Definitely broken.
Come on. Come on.
He's here! Hey, Dad.
Hey buddy. I'm so happy to see you.
I was so worried,
I thought I'd never see you again.
I knew I could count on you.
I was naive to think
I could do this alone.
Forget that.
Let's finish this thing, together.
We've got to leave.
X-TRAKT is gonna blow up
this place,
and I'd rather not be down here for it.
I can't go anywhere.
My foot is broken.
Okay, I'm on it.
Thank you.
Hey, we're a family,
and we stick together.
Now let's get out of here.
Sir, we've just hit target depth.
Finally.
Now prepare the "Big Daddy".
Prepare the BD-416.
Ouch.
I mean prepare the Big Daddy.
Hold on. Do you hear that?
- Yeah.
- Uh, no.
It's coming from over there.
That's the bomb.
If that thing blows,
this entire mine will collapse.
We've gotta disarm it.
- They don't look friendly.
- I doubt they saw us.
Shh.
Sir, there's something you have to see.
Look.
They're not gonna compromise this.
Make sure they don't get out alive.
Uh, sir, just to clarify the air here,
and please do not take offense.
Umm. Are you asking me to kill them?
Because that's not really
in my job description.
Give me that job description.
Arlo, get over here.
I thought you'd never ask.
- Move over, pal.
- Hey!
Time to see
what these drone babies can do!
Uh-oh, run!
I was wrong,
they definitely noticed us.
- Really?
- No sassing.
Ahh. Oof.
- Over here.
- Woah.
Oof.
This is too old.
Dad, the drone's cutting the cables.
Oh no.
Phew. That worked out well.
Ugh.
I hate roller coasters.
- Let's take a ride.
- Okay, let's go.
As long as the tunnels haven't caved in,
this thing has got to lead somewhere.
Uh-oh.
It's following us.
Pump really fast.
Ahh. Woah.
Should we slow down?
This isn't feeling that safe.
We're trapped in an abandoned mine,
and psychopaths with crazy drones
are trying to kill us!
Let's see how they deal
with this drone!
Grr.
Damn! Drone down.
I lost one of my babies.
Technically, they're my babies.
I pay for them.
- Woah.
- Adam.
Ahh.
- Gotcha.
- Ahh.
Oh no!
- Hey!
- Dad.
Over here.
- Oh... Jim.
- Watch out.
- Dad!
- Adam!
Alright.
There's more.
Oh no.
Ahh.
Ohh.
Okay, we're safe.
They just took out our last drone.
There's no escaping the "Big Daddy".
It's not scheduled to detonate
for another day.
We must clear
our machines and...
Change of plans.
Y'all got 10 minutes.
Oh, this is insane.
Anything left in this valley
will be drowned
in a beautiful ocean of oil.
All teams evacuate now.
Ten minutes until detonation.
All personnel evacuate now.
The explosions set the oil on fire.
Uh guys...
We have to jump it.
We need speed. Hang on!
Don't breathe in.
That smoke is toxic.
Daylight! We're going to make it.
Phew.
Finally, fresh air.
Oh, I'm back online.
Let's see what the world thinks
of X-TRAKT's plans!
Come on, come on.
Dial-up was faster than this.
Oh no!
Now isn't the time
to be posting selfies.
I'm kind of doing
something here.
Slow down.
I'm trying.
You need to pull harder.
Hm.
Good job, honey.
A river. We must jump.
- I can't.
- Yeah.
Don't get wet.
Ahh!
- Dad!
- Adam!
Where's your mother?
Help!
Shelly!
Ahh.
- Waterfall!
- Oh no!
Mom! Dad!
Are you okay?
Yes, we're fine!
Evacuate. Evacuate.
Time to detonation:
1 minute, 30 seconds.
Get out of the valley fast!
Get to higher ground.
But what about you?
Everything is going to be okay, go now!
Time to detonation,
1 minute, 15 seconds.
Sixty seconds to detonation.
There's little time.
We must move.
I hope Adam made it to safety.
I'm sure he is fine.
Thirty seconds to detonation.
- Adam!
- Oh no.
Ugh.
Okay, how do I get down there?
Fifteen seconds to detonation.
I hope this works!
Woah!
10, 9...
- Woah.
- 8, 7, 6...
- Woah!
- 5, 4...
Come on.
- 3...
- Come on.
2...
1...
- What's going on?
- Disarmed.
Disarmed. Disarmed.
He did it!
Woah, man.
No! That's not possible.
What are you waiting for?
Start it up again.
It's not that simple, sir.
If it's shut off at the source,
the only way to detonate it
is another detonation.
Can't we use
a small fracking bomb for this?
Yes, I suppose that would have
enough explosive charge
to trigger the BD-416...
Uh, I mean, the "Big Daddy".
Arlo, can you handle that device?
Sure thing.
I used one to blow my old foster home
when I was a kid. It works.
Great. Let's go then.
Ouch.
I need a break!
- Huh?
- Oh, what now?
- They got another bomb.
- No!
Listen up.
After tossing the bomb,
get back up the cliff
before oil floods the valley.
How long do we have?
Have you ever run
to bathroom in a hurry? Yeah,
that fast.
And the hero rode in
on his mighty steed!
Look! We gotta stop them.
Step on it.
It's already stepped on.
This could help.
We're coming, Adam.
What kind of circus is this?
Oh, never mind,
the bear, he's harmless.
Hey, back off!
Lean back. I'll deal with him.
Wilbur, watch out.
- Ow. Ouch.
- Trapper!
No, not again.
Hang on, Wilbur.
Give it to them, Wilbur.
Don't worry about me.
I'm a goner anyway.
No!
Hi-ya.
Well, well, well.
Look who's here.
Mister Big Fool himself.
Long time no see. Now, give it to me.
- Never.
- Ha.
- You'd rather blow us all up?
- This ends now.
You see?
That's why you hippies will never win.
There's no room for dreamers out here.
Your type...
Get off my land. Get out of here.
The light's still flashing.
Shouldn't you turn that off?
Oh. Shoot, I can't stop it.
Plan B!
It was close
but you did good, son.
Huh. Too close for comfort,
that's for sure.
Don't you ever do that again.
You're safe, I'm so proud of you.
Huh? Guys, what happened?
- You wrecked the camper.
- Uh-uh... It's not my fault.
Trapper? Where's Trapper?
I'm right here.
This is Channel Six News.
We'd like to ask you some questions.
It worked, they saw my videos.
Hey Mandrake, smile. You're on camera.
Why are they up there?
This is restricted airspace!
To show people
what you did.
So you know, I uploaded the video
of you talking
about destroying here.
Pfft, we'll say it's fake news,
deny the whole thing.
As they say:
The truth will set you free.
Not in your case.
You're going to jail.
Hey look, the cops.
Uh-oh!
Catch me if you can.
What? Ah!
♪ Do we know
where the light is the brightest? ♪
♪ Do we know how to clear
what the fear is? ♪
Get off my land.
Buzz off.
You understand what that means?
It means get... off... my... land.
Go for it. Dinner time.
I don't like human flesh.
But a fresh snow rabbit...
Here we go again.
I'm Becky Dabmore,
and you're watching Good Morning World.
I'm here on location in Alaska,
where Bigfoot
and his family have saved Rocky Valley
from an environmental disaster.
So Dr. Harrison,
it looks like you found a way
to make the world better.
Thanks Becky,
but I didn't save this place.
It was my son, Adam.
And what about you, Adam,
what do you have to say?
My Dad was right,
one person really can make a difference.
The government is working
to protect this land.
Nobody can ever
drill here again.
Mom, you must be so proud?
I am. I'm proud of the whole family.
Woah! Ahh!
I'm okay.
Oh boy.
So, I grab the oil company CEO,
and I look him
in his beady little eyes, and I say,
"It's time to end this crude behavior."
Get it? Cause sometimes unrefined oil
is called crude.
I've got to tell you.
I don't think it's funny.
The point is, I saved the day,
and am also the hero of this story.
Fine. Wilbur helped too.
And Adam I guess.
But it was mostly me.
Oh, whoops. Sorry, bad toss.
Normally I'd be upset.
But I admit,
you make a great flapjack.
Keep 'em coming.
I'm gonna be late.
See you all tonight.
- Have fun.
- Say hi to Emma.
Oh la la.
Mom, don't encourage them.
Don't encourage who?
Hi Emma... Perfect timing.
What are you watching?
When you uploaded your videos,
you uploaded all your videos.
Uh-oh.
Emma, it turns out, life is short.
I wish I would've told you how I felt...
Hey!
Will you go out with me?
Never mind them, let's get out of here.
Oh.
Our boy's all grown up.
Can I get another pancake over here?
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ When you been around a bit ♪
♪ But you never really got to know
the half of it, yeah ♪
♪ Maybe you could take a stand ♪
♪ For something that you wanted
but it's out of hand, yeah ♪
♪ Well okay, I'm not all of that ♪
♪ And it probably wasn't written
in the stars above, deal ♪
♪ It's all that I did ♪
♪ And I go and do it my way
My way ♪
♪ Never think about what they say
They say ♪
♪ And enough is enough ♪
♪ Give it all that you got ♪
♪ You go and do it your way
Your way ♪
♪ Whatever it was, it won't be
Won't be ♪
♪ And whatever will be
is all you want it to be ♪
♪ I said it's gonna be... yours ♪
♪ Tell me that it's all you want ♪
♪ And I'll leave you in a minute,
oh yeah, I'll be gone ♪
♪ Tell me that it's all you need ♪
♪ And there's nothing else you wanted,
I will let you be ♪
♪ Tell me that it's what you see ♪
♪ And I will tell you
how it never really was for me ♪
♪ And deal ♪
♪ It's all that I did ♪
♪ Then I go and do it my way
My way ♪
♪ Never think about what they say
They say ♪
♪ And enough is enough ♪
♪ Give it all that you got ♪
♪ You go and do it your way
Your way ♪
♪ Whatever it was, it won't be
Won't be ♪
♪ And whatever will be
is all you want it to be ♪
♪ I said it's gonna be... ♪
♪ Yours ♪
♪ I said it's gonna be... yours ♪
♪ Yeah, it's gonna be... yours ♪
♪ Yours ♪
♪ I said it's gonna be yours ♪
♪ Don't sit down, turn around ♪
♪ And let's get out of this town ♪
♪ Where the people have scars ♪
♪ Just from livin' ♪
♪ And let's drive on down below ♪
♪ On this solemn country road ♪
♪ While city lights fade fast
in the night ♪
♪ Searching high, searching low ♪
♪ We don't know yet where to go ♪
♪ But our faces are pointing ♪
♪ To the target ♪
♪ No matter what we left behind ♪
♪ We'll keep moving till we find ♪
♪ Another place without a name
and not a sign ♪
♪ Let's get lost in the open
just to find ♪
♪ Our lost ♪
♪ Peace of mind ♪
♪ Let's go out ♪
♪ Find a heaven in the world ♪
♪ To claim ♪
♪ Our peace of mind ♪
♪ Out in the open ♪
♪ Ohhh... ♪
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6xngy
Help other users to choose the best subtitles