How can the average person like ah
This kid is Zhenhen
Admit defeat that kind of enthusiasm
He actually put a three pupils who started school students playing Pianjiabuliu
record of inquiry
A small piece of the head can not
His parents how it was
His father is the national team of taekwondo athletes
His mother is also the national team gymnast
Olympic taekwondo silver medal for South Korea won the silver medal in taekwondo glory for Jintai Sheng
Two people were killed on the spot because of a traffic accident
Truck driver fatigue driving
Directly over the center line
I do not know is fortunate or unfortunate
In this boy survived
And then I heard that you are looking for such a child
You know this is a state secret, right
You heard it can play ah
Even those three days of brothers played Pianjiabuliu
Your father is called Jin Taisheng it
Do you know my dad
Olympic Taekwondo silver medalist
Jintai Sheng
He can have all my wins glory
What is your aspiration
As when a taekwondo athlete like you dad
You have such a temper against soft
Gold is also mention
I just wanted to draw comics
Cartoon
Why do you want to draw comics ah
Cartoons make me feel better
During this time painting in
I'll forget everything
Can not remember those terrible memories
What nonsense to say it
the man
How can you care about these sections
Must embrace ambitious dream is
what
Cartoon
Do not you think your father did
You win glory for the country
I gotta take a trip you up
NIS anti-terrorism Security Agency
Jason Lee
Jason Lee Height 187cm Weight 91kg Birthday 1974/02/17 Nationality unknown unable to confirm whether it is a terrorist organization criminal record, 1999 terrorist attack in the Moscow train derailed chain explosion terrorist attack in the Middle East 2000 in 2000 kidnapping of Kazakh women in 2001 in West Africa drug trade in 2003 to provide weapons to the African pirate bomb terrorist attack in 2004 the Bank of Korea
The shuttle in the Middle East and Central Asia, North Korea
Just based on current intelligence point of view has been mastered
Has been involved in 38 cases of kidnapping and terrorist attack
Plain and transnational crime, terrorists
Although nationality is not clear
But industry are considered to Korean
Who a few years ago in Vladivostok
And our agents had played against Arjun
Although we failed to win
Gave the other party left an indelible damage
This person is the mastermind behind the terrorist attack yesterday, a bomb Han Bank
According to the current understanding of the term
Casualties reached 27 people
The midst of sadness is
We were egged on by this success caught
Detonated the bomb that person's brother
It is made
Our trump card
Arjun alone to complete this task
Arjun
We must get rid of Jason
Even for those innocent victims of nationals
Yes
Force like couples latent senior vice undercover
2004 story collection plan specific regional story collection open call
Code 9 immediately return to look
Go on like this it is not afraid to die
Even if they have to kill him to let him move ah
But these guys have killed dozens of innocent lives
I received the news of his Gegejiesen now in Busan
Soon fled abroad
Before he must leave our waters
Get rid of him
Small Zhe
Big now ah
Saying how do you come here
This is also part of their training
Optimistic about the small Zhe
Yes
He's about to inherit the mantle of your kite shield
Next ace kite shield
The older you are my idol
What idol ah
But you and I are being led by the nose top Bale
I have not been led by the nose
I was selected
Yes
Not breathe
Ready to fight infiltration
We must get rid of that guy tonight
Yes
Three minutes from the landing site
This would be too dangerous
Is not to apply to change the plan is ah
Do you think this will stop it on top
As planned
If I died of this task
To use this to do my portrait
How could such a thing
After all, the fate of enigmatic
Arjun
Too dangerous to quickly open the parachute
What's wrong
This so not open
Hurry hurry umbrella open ah
Arjun
National owe you too much
We will never
Forget your sacrifice
collective
salute
I really respect you
Yes
So you like to draw
Now you can in the sky
Enjoy the painting
Now you can finally start a new life
I want my dream coming
I will be the explosion of red cartoonist
On ah
On the upper
15 years
the eighth comic encourage new Grand Prix Award
Ruined
How was filled with drama ah no time
Kyu Wan editor
Hey
A teacher who gave me this you
I say that you want to draw in the end what it comes up
Really Sorry
I also want to send you as soon as possible
May be behind the story is too boring
This time I'm really going down Henzhao ah
Removed behind you serialize
What do you mean
How can withdraw it
How much money did I get
What I was most cases, you know ah
That our case it
Not Rated did not say traffic
Not time delivery
In the end you know
The reason has been no problem that I can help you clutching
This course I know
I have been grateful to you
Count me ask you the least time delivery bar
Really Sorry
Before midnight I will send you in the past
Hey you this enemy
I said that these costs should be promptly post it
This thing I have to do to run errands
Sorry forgot to catch a turnaround gave
I urge you to make money you have
I finally put money back
You ran like a hand
Even this thing you do not you
Really really hate you so much
Dear Do you think you fire too
Tight with anger here ...
Wow you first sit down
You sit down and I can help you loose
You will become tired of
This trend continues you will become tired of
Oh, it's hard loose yet
It hurts
stop
Hey I do not want to be late coming
Today I will go to post
Must pay
Good to excellent British call their children to school to prepare meals
do not worry
That one…
You do not forget something wrong
Jia Ying recently, it seems no appetite
Have to buy toilet paper and seafood
These can be enough ah
Your work go okay
I've been trying for a
Do not worry quite smoothly
Ok
You busy Kazakhstan
I am a busy man
Jia Ying
Hey I am not saying this is not good to sleep wearing
Get up to go to school
Going to be late ah
Look at this girl
- do not do it - do not ah
stand up
Do it
- Do it - up up
do not
This is the night you patronize sleep and write rap lyrics ah
I'm not saying do not go to bed at night light long a
Dad you do not also patronize the thing to bed and cartoons
Dad make money make money ah
You obviously can not make some money
Mom was not all day long training Well
Ah this woman in the end all day with the kids say Hu
Jia Ying
My dad got it you can also do
Before you said you wanted it keyboard
Your dad I just all of a sudden fire
Will give you buy the best keyboard
dare you laugh
They might
I will be your first step on the "give me money" to win the championship
Note: South Korean rap give me the money athletics program
what did you say
Well hello eating before you go
Ah I'm going to be late
This girl is really bigger and more like her mom
I always feel that the end of something worse
The "what" in the end what is it
Really Chousi me
Damn
Really
upload NAVER mail attachment "Shaolin Temple comedy" 13 words ...
has been successfully sent messages
editor Kim Kyu Wan teacher, what time can not pay on time, ah? You have just sent a! Sorry issued late
just have to send you up! Sorry issued late! !
Together bizarre case from happening again
eyes were again found bodies dug
At a port in Busan
Male body was found in his eyes dug a
Police in the investigation
Shortly after midnight today
eyes were again found bodies dug
A worker found the body near the site
The deceased was unidentified men in their thirties
Police have commissioned NSC search for autopsy
Investigating the identity of the deceased
Wow this murderous murderous ah
Said the investigation will likely turn to a direction which later also how to raise children ah
Serial murder direction
Murder news reports
NAVER diffuse Comedy Network updated if the temple 13
Please, God
Buy one pair have not seen eye to this network Man
ah huh Buy one pair have not seen this network Man's eyes seemed to dig up my eyes have seen an unprecedented double for slag, the idea that the artist's life, too, not here shit. I even painted their feet than the top of this strong Oh I agree this is rubbish wow really please to apologize garbage garbage can recycle this thing actually serialized? ? ? Author quit painting it now is able to draw Emaoagou network Man? What a pity to waste my time hehehe
I really want to dig up this pair of eyes watched
Unprecedented for slag
The author of the idea that life is too Do not talk shit here
I even painted their feet stronger than this
This is rubbish
Please apologize to the trash
Garbage can be recycled at least
This stuff actually still serialized
Author quit painting it
Now is able to draw network Man Tun Town
It is a pity I spent time slide the scroll bar
Anyhow, there is still much of the ...
Anyhow, there are still big fans of the author
Come on
Anyhow, there are still big fans of, Come on Come on! !
Refuel
Anyhow, there are still big fans of, Come on Come on! ! You are the author do? I am not ah! This is another thing that you ID to the comments section when the navy ah Oh really say why you want to live entirely self-directed thing Oh ages have grown to asshole blew it dead Oh really lost
You are the author do
I am not ah
exactly
This is another old you to the comments section when the navy ah
Why should say really alive
The feeling is entirely self-directed and acted in Well
All of them are long ass Well
Really blew it lost the dead
Or keep track of their IP killed them all
Jin Jiaying
Hey
Walk do not have eyes ah
Sorry
Damn
Damn scared me
I have not told you not to sound too much Well
Moment forgot
Too immersed in the music
Last thing is not
Get you into trouble
This I confiscated
Dad You're smoking it
It had drawn
I'll tell my mother
Etc., etc
Dad had very tired today, this day
Today is not the day to upload comic thing
When it would write off
Mom over there
Hey wait for me Well
Why it
Doing what
Hey hey
To feed the slippers off
Hey
Wait for me Well
That one…
Have you seen my father do to upload comic
Ok
you look at it
Why also Kanla
You do not have the words are on time every point Kanla
You've worked hard dad
What Headshake
how about it
To be honest it
I was with my friends to see
How they say -
Super boring
Or else you Dad
Tell your own story straight
Like "give me money" as
Eh
Those rappers on stage to sing their own stories how cool
This can be the same thing
I will use my own story to write rap lyrics
Dad you draw your own story Well
Lay it
If my story
But will subvert the entire South Korea
Jia Ying
Dad I'm off
Ok
Ah dad
You do not always see the comments will hurt
Do not look
Hundred percent injured
Yay
Even though is
Hi Pak editor
Ah teacher who
Note compiled Park Wan Kyu
That "Comedy Shaolin Temple"
If it is over the next serial
Lose all the rest of it
Eh
What kind of truth
I will wait and increasingly repercussions
Thanks to you I can be famous ah
There are twenty thousand light Comments
I went down the river is a curse
Not ah Park Editor
Beg you
You can not withdraw ah
No
- Frankly, I always thought that one day you will be red - not editor ah Park
- will be red - will increasingly have repercussions
- I'm holding this belief persist to this day - Pak editor
But evidently afraid to die
Ask you to help me
Ah can not be removed
Now I also do not trust their own intuition
Then wait a little bar
- have removed it - Pak editor
Hey
That ... Hey
Damn feed
Do not
Beware of falling objects
Hey
Brat
Oh Hey Look Look
You have to look at this spade shovel
Oh Hey ah ah
Will play silly games
Hello all gray ah
This is when you shovel the play ah
Hey you
Did not go to the military have served you
Oh Hey
If another lazy're dead
When I was lazy
But for that guy
I have to give you bastard ...
Stop hand movements
what did you just say
Call me now
What asshole
Hey asshole
Spade asshole
Hey kid shovel
Do not stare at me
Not allowed to stare at ...
What does look
Shake it
Note: a similar pronunciation and jerk
Shake it Shake it Shake it
I was just singing to the
You know the kid
What the United States is not the song Well
Shake it Shake it
I'll do
okay
Shake it
prohibited near
large companies have almost basic wage level Note: talking here cartoonist Goldwind
Almost the equivalent of the basic wage base salary of big business right
I could not even give her daughter can not afford to buy a keyboard
fool
Fool you doing in the end
... then began serialization start making money
N after the website began serialization income rose Note: Talking cartoonist flag here is safe 84
My mom bought a house
mother's home to help his mother pay off debts + + + mother's midsize sedan flag An 84 rental
Help my mother pay off debt
My mom bought a midsize sedan
Then find yourself a long-term lease of a house
Damn I can not compare with the flag in the end where the security 84
really say too TM ugly Oh I have to go with the "back to school King" flag soothe the nerves of the eye wash this talk really ... even bad reviews have pity Come on ... serialize it stopped ... (knees) I saw one point oh oh
Offscum
This is simply slag slag
This is the age of slag slag are long asshole blew it lost the dead no way this thing is painting what rubbish recycling
This is no way to recycle stuff
ah you go to the flag of the 84 security companies to clean it
It feels like looking at trash
really a waste of mental torture network traffic Man appears!
Hey no appetite to eat
You might as well go ah company of flag An 84 clean it
What a waste I see with this flow
All of them are long ass Well
Why should say really alive
Those rappers on stage to sing their own stories how cool
Dad you draw your own story Well
Lay it
Damn
These guys when I was what people
What do you know
I is the story behind MD
I'd want you to look at
Who I was
You dead
Hello everyone
I am about to teach you the
Legend devil instructor one thousand Dekui
Here you have to be reborn as the guardian of the country's top shield
Who if outdated
It will return to normal reality again gutter
Too strong for everyone
Must not fall
No matter what kind of situation encountered
Will never be back
Good job done
Not even sniffing death
You must be reborn as the strongest shield kite
Tatetonbi
Invest 50 billion national budget
Our country is the top weapon
You are the weapon
arms
Is your
You finally come today
In order to become a true kite shield
There is one final hurdle
Warfare,
Then how was it
I got it it
Worse
My eyes really nothing wrong
Now the ace kite shield
Is you
Shangbadunyuan
Arjun
assassinated agents Arjun
Some people want to come to you
Tired of it
Ah have to sober up
I called to see how you do not play it
Husband
Tired of it
No effort to sit right
Sit here
What
Me
Recently force you into a corner of the bar
Sorry
What's wrong with you
seriously
I knew that one day you failed to do so
succeed
What to do
Ah really delicious
You simply that the new network Man Chan burst
Why is he so good topic to hold back now ah
New network Man
what
Honey is not sober you do it
Look at this
you because of the country's top guard shield in this rebirth
This was a good fried
It was a good fried
You see ah
This time you finally fire
kite shield plan part1: a group of humanoid weapons trained as children
How this upload this
I see you asleep
You have to help tidy up the hair
I do well it
Are you crazy
Why send this
I draw these are not to be issued
What do you draw strength
How to help you do you still noisy
Hey you look at these reviews
what the circumstances, I seem to smell the author's masterpiece greatly on drugs? I see super nice dizziness, more quickly it! ! ! The money first time, a small venture to say that money is better than much of what this comic masterpiece masterpiece few words ...
This parade is the first time you see it
Really is not a joke
what
Please help me take down come on I would really be dead
This is the first time you'll ever get the number one network Man
I actually removed
I say you are not crazy ah
That is ... I was drunk accidentally passed up
Beg you
- save my life now - is not it
Drunk before painting it
I see you is entirely an artist ah
Next time also taking advantage of drunken continue to draw
I will offer unlimited refills for the services you move forward
Pak editor beg you beg you
I really have difficulties ah beg you
Do not fucking nonsense
Then rush to prepare more continued to do it
I'm busy now
Pak editor
Well you first, and so
Blah blah blah
Oh
Hey
Ah representatives
"Assassination agents Arjun" it
Have you seen the ah
Damn
Yes Yes Yes
I was not long ago that
A teacher who will one day be red
Yes ah Well today is not that day
Yes Yes Yes
Yes Yes
Pak editor beg you ...
I go to
Quickly roll back to painting
Damn matter
My daughter should not bring an umbrella bar
Damn
Secondary light Kam
Oh good English ...
Jia Ying
Hey Dad
Hello
Hey do you want to go to my house to play will
My dad gave me to buy a VR it
really
Ok
But my dad did not come to it
Before every time it rains he will come and take my
Today, your dad may not come
But your dad is still drawing cartoons right
Yes
Let's go
absolutely not allowed to see
Jin Jiaying's dare turn down a dead man ...
What money is counted in the end
Money for our family in terms of how it is so far away
She said to me
Just learn to happiness
But I know
The truth of this world
Eternal truth is
Something people can live a carefree is
MONEY
Everything is money because money
No money will be sad suffering hardship
The reason why Mom and Dad will fight
The reason why my mother always drunk
If money can solve everything
It would not have
So I decided war "Give me the money."
I won the first prize to pay off his father's debt
I hasten to successfully buy a house
show me the money for my parents
Now take up the microphone
show me the money
Anyway, sooner or later we have to die
Even his wife and children to take care of bad
What's important
Vladivostok
Look
I pose this chic
From now on I will reputed Quartet
What the fuck
Come catch that kid
Good for you
Kill him
This monster kid
Damn quick step on the gas
what's the situation
Arjun I will kill you
Arjun
bang
What are you doing
Look at this look at this
Bravo
Wow
My God
This great bar
hurry up
what is this
excuse me
National Intelligence Service one thousand Dekui
Some people threatened to launch terrorist attack
Terrorist attack
It was a message in the Blue House Home
Threatened to detonate a bomb at nine o'clock tomorrow morning to launch terrorist attack
According to the tracking of IP
Prisoners in an hour before leaving here have spoken
Where this machine in
Your old universe handsome boss 18 it
Yes
But your uncle really agents of the National Intelligence Agency do
I feel that you do not
Do not lie to our friends
You are not agents uncle ah
Comic saw the national intelligence officer looks super cool
what's up
This is ugly right
Look
One thousand Dekui
With the name of the devil instructor like it
Hey really
Shield devil kite instructor one thousand Dekui
This is how you know
This is the national level secrets
Now I do not know how people ah kite shield
Recently shield kite then fire
what
You look
devil instructor one thousand Dekui this guy, much worse ...
what is this
not this
kite shield plan part1: a group of humanoid weapons trained as children
This in the end is which guy painting
Kite shield plan humanoid weapons training as children do
You bring a child into an orphanage from assassin yet
When this is the real end of the island or what
I just received a call VIP rushed over
One thousand Secretary
You explain
This project is scrapped a long time ago
還有部分不是事實
不知道是哪個傢伙寫的
內容包含很多造假和誇張的成分
-尤其是關於我的故事 -怎麼
你怕了嗎
如果被媒體發現了苗頭你要怎麼辦
我們怎麼知道 他們會寫出什麼樣的報導出來
真是
瞧瞧這幫人
你們真的不知道盾鳶計劃嗎
這裡有多少人 是真的不知道這個項目的
現在大家都假裝不知情嗎
這個小人到底會是誰呢
我好像察覺到這個小人是誰了
加入漫畫裡所有作戰的特工
It is not just a kid
You are saying that you Arjun
- Arjun is fighting agents of death - not the corpse did not find it
You are all kept in the dark of him
Implying that he is pretending dead yet
Well, this was too outrageous
If he really is disguised as dead if
He had no reason to expose their story ah
So his identity will be exposed ah
Of course, the reason
What is not drawing money Figure
Last week our agents has been killed
Eyes were poached
We sent a search team is looking for criminals
But this how the ...
The special agent, like Arjuna, like a kite shield plan
Plus agents before being killed also
Yes
Taking advantage of this time to kite shield plan exposed to comics
The timing is too coincidental not
You are saying that our agents have been killed this cartoon associated with it
It is able to sell all the money in the world
If this man is painting the words of Arjun
He was betrayed by his colleagues
Kite Shield plans in agents
He also had a relationship with a good guy now
After the planned obsolescence
Aci agents placed in the other team
He was the last to leave the kite shield
It is very beneficial to grab that guy
He quickly recall
Hey brother, it is the
It looks beautiful for words
To Come
you are so handsome! must work hard!
Refuel
What to do? What to do? What to do
He looked me up
- I'm really going crazy - how to do it
He is not now going to see ah
Look how handsome ah
Secretary
Sasha is not here
In Russia fainted how the guy will be here
The taste
All week I did not really wash
How can the situation as a trump card beggar ah
What are you talking nonsense
Who says you are a trump card
- quickly rejoin - you rejoin
Sasha appeared yet
Where is that kid in
The real trump card appeared
Arjun seems to be alive
what
Arjun
He really super handsome
correct
I received your mind
Share of good heart never lose Oh
Ok
My goodness
Brother, I love you
Park Wan Kyu
I'm surprised
You people how to come in without knocking
A little education are not
You are responsible for the assassination of agents who do Arjun
Yes, I was the person in charge
Is there a problem
we
NIS you
This one
Looked a little familiar
But I did not recognize
You give me carefully optimistic
The guy who painted it
Oh, I felt that a teacher who looks a bit like
It would seem that look different
Because this is not the same hairstyle
So let you take a closer look
A teacher who is not so handsome type ah
You do not have a teacher photo
Yes, not at all
His private life is taboo exposure
Taboo private life exposed
This guy is right Arjuna
A teacher who made mistakes
I want to know the ins and outs of things
This guy is a spy
Why do fierce inter-dish dish
A teacher who is sort of spy ah
Simply outrageous
Who do birthday today
This is a hidden camera right
How jokes
Who you kidding
Ligament ligament hurts
You have to help us look
Hi Pak editor
A teacher who really you've worked hard
The words of praise are also repercussions burst
But I am a bit flattered ah
Has always been on hiatus
Such sudden fire
You little prick
Can not you see we are busy hands busy feet do
Hang up quickly hang up the phone
- I'm sorry - you little prick quickly
You lazy once again I would not have mercy
Quickly dig
Even blow enough by guys
Or just put that guy dig into
parking
Parking Parking
You seen this man
It seems to be the front man
- Arjun predecessors - this guy do
Yes
- is the guy to go to catch up - catch him
You're right Jin Fengjun
what
My name is Kim Soo Hyuk you got the wrong guy, right
You're Jin Fengjun ah
You should not call you
Arjun agents assassinated
You're going to trip us up
Jin Fengjun
I'm not saying the
Do not be fooled that this kid
Hurry to arrest him
He walked up to the other point of view ah
Oh shit
Quickly from another angle
empty
Group B Group C
Do not go with a low profile proud
He may have a big difference with you
Jia Ying wife has not come back ah class
We want to run away quickly back pack bags
Why are you ah
I painted the cartoon
Why do you upload that
That is my story
I was the assassination of agents Arjun
This is what it means
Mina is afraid of the name can not be used
Change the name of it
By the way my wife you do not want plastic surgery
Take this opportunity to the whole point of it pretty
Hey you are not a big drinking day
You this kid is really Niwai
Do not talk nonsense
I do in class
Now the focus is not on No School
Shut up noisy dead
I said I was assassinated agents Arjun
Wife
How not believe it
I was Arjun ah
This does not
You are right aci
When you grow up ah almost did not recognize ...
Caught
The villain
A teacher who really do spy
What do
who are you
The guy working here now
I have just told you
In the end you want to do ah
NIS is very great yet
NIS
What it is
Why did you smoke in the office
How did these people do a little ritual
Are you saying that the people came to NIS yet
Wait
You are Jason cartoons appear we do
This detail is in place ah
You are imitating it
I looked a lot like
I'm looking for people who draw the comics
As if we do not know the way
Not that
They say you'll know
That one
Involving personal message inconvenient to tell ...
They would want me to become your face
it hurts
help me
the third anti-terrorism Security Agency headquarters
Grab a civilian
Surprising with such high power stun guns
You do seniors are civilians
I really want to be like the older people
You can deceive us so how ah
I apologize for not telling you in advance
I also have no way
During this time I really thought the older generation dies
Why would you do
Because there is no other way to die except to resign
You still do that it recently
Times have changed
Since the older generation disappears
After a few years of that plan was scrapped completely
I was the last kite shield
That's great
You are like me pulled over ah
Worry about yourself first
Now you because of leaking a confidential arrested
Long time no captain
Why did you betray us
What kind of drawing cartoons on the grounds that
If I say you will believe me
Why did you leave you in the end
I pay so much for you
Because I want to live their ideal appearance
Even if only once
Your ideal life right
So your ideal life is a mere cartoons right
Cartoons how the
I told you many times
This is my dream ah
That kid is really
I spent much of the budget How about you
You do mere cartoons
You do this guy kidding
you guys
I have full use of the ah
You know this time how much my hands stained with blood
enough
it is good
As the cost of leaks shield kite receive how much money
That's just my comic drunk upload
I have no intention
Monthly income of less than 500 000
As a long face lost enough of it
You no sense of responsibility Boy
What also can not afford child birth
Disgrace face rub his wife's salary
You pair of virtue
So the idea of ​​it there to make a killing
Both before and after to get on the ah
How much you sell with colleagues of
The ability to compile the novel a no ah
Brats what you say
You look at me like kidding me
You would want your daughter has become such an orphan
You brats
- I'm going to kill him - not
let me go
You talk about it before we went calm
snakes
It snakes
You do signal poisonous snakes
Otherwise, with the older generation is a group of people you
Is the killer still Intelligencer
My wife
註：與老婆發音相似
马努拉 large
This is where
My wife and kids mom
Never for so long did not answer the phone
Let me answer it right
You also know that this is not right
Hey wife
Do not you listen to me talk
Otherwise, your wife will die
How to feel back again
Jia Ying father is how these people will be going on
If you want to save your wife will do as I say
Do you understand
I know
I am not satisfied with your answer
I know I'm listening
You are now NIS seized on right
Give you 20 minutes
Now with one thousand Secretary to the tunnel to Kowloon
This is a bit difficult task
is it hard
I let you easily point it
With that kid out right now
Nightly five minutes
This woman would be less a finger
After the finger is gone
After no finger
What do the next break
毒蛇
has it ended
The agents asked your home address
Sister-in-law to which I will be the
I am a traitor to
I Spy
I confess called captain Come
Secretary
Arjun senior said he confessed to espionage
what
But he wanted dialogue with the Secretary
Well what happened
It also gave me a
Sorry
This madman
You know this kid I would like this
What is your real purpose is to
Threw the gun
If you really want so you can not restore the
Immediately give up
Threw the gun
You want to see it head with holes
Come in
Threw the gun
You all right
You think I'm all right
Shoot this kid
First open shot
Hey
It fired a single shot shot
Threw the gun
This waste
Well not let you open shot boy
Whoops please
Building blockade immediately
Do not let the kid go out
Hey what are you doing
Hey
Hey this untie
I'm not a prisoner
Do you deliberately caught it
The purpose is to kidnap me
My wife has been kidnapped
I say
- by whom - I do not know
Say no to bring you to kill my wife
and then
I do want you to pay out
If you shut me out, then will die
You do not very clear
關機
The phone to pay out
Will be located
No I did not bring
I did not bring
No
This boy is a boy
Where did you touch it with
Rude boy
Good car
Our goal is to train the best agents assassinated
I'm ready to
That guy is a murder weapon was covered arms
Allow all agents were shot and killed
found it
Crossroads to the northeast direction from Ilwon
Transport position
A Group B at full speed to keep
Hey escape escape escape
Hey Hey car coming
毒蛇
Kowloon right now entering the tunnel
How there are so many to follow your tails
In the tunnel gave me the air
My wife all right
Worry about it
Come on then quickly
Enter the tunnel
I gave the rest of the team with the inside
Secretary
Find me
Really to a lot of damn
Agents assassinated the legendary Arjun
I listen to your stories are boring
Because it is the legendary ah
Let me look at the legendary strength of it
In this effort it
It let me down ah
I've been in more than a clever retreat
Honestly it alone
Why look for a job also out
Release brats
Such court death it rude for seniors
Boy you go on to great things out
What ah boy get out of the brats
I'm sorry you got to run
Borrow your car
Uncle you get going
Get going quickly
Do not shoot Do not shoot
Help
Get rid of
Who do you think
Since the other party wants you
There is definitely a grudge with you people
I say
Since it was first kidnapped your wife
Should tell you it deeper rancor
It may first kidnapped your wife ah
I have no wife
Divorce yet
Hey are not up to now have not ...
That you are not married no wife
Now my wife was kidnapped
Who says I can not get married
I am married with a country
What is the crime of the State
This is all your fault
This is what I blame
You because your comic disclose confidential
Was such a thing happened
Ah yes
what happened
Today is the day comic strip
what
The captain and his brother Jason has appeared
Ah can not appear to be a major event
Wait
A major event
Damn it hit yesterday laser
Ah my waist
A teacher
I was really guilty of a capital offense
I have to pay out your home address
How to wear them
Remember you told me
Looks like you works exactly like Jason
Jason
The madman it
Good scary wounds and burns
A teacher who really sorry
They threatened me to dig up my eyes
I do not know what to do
it's not your fault
A teacher
Whether human or NIS of those guys
Is looking for the non-serialized file
So I did not say absolutely nothing
Even dug my eyes and I can not give
Let me keep
- Well done Pak editor - well done
- Park editor awesome well done - thank Pak editor
Free to eat a meal of it
The next words have tortured captain Jason brother's picture
If this is a major event I spread
Thank you
This is a teacher who works hard to create
Of course, have available the
So I just uploaded
what
what did you say
Where is spread
A teacher
Finally saw the dawn
How hard it is to get a chance
Hey you crazy
How can upload it
Quickly removed to brats
Hey what you say
Who do you think you are
Do not let me upload brats
You crazy
Quickly removed to you this crazy
Why should upload
What neuropathy
You brats to stay that do not move
I'm born kid-Team
I can put you labeled the shutters opened a joint
What blinds fold yourself go
Fold kid yourself go
NAVER網漫 暗殺特工阿俊第4話已更新
Out out
額啊
Where is it
Dead
I have it
I see no
死了
Simon
My brother
That you should mistake it
You got the wrong person
You do not Arjun wife
No
My husband does not call Jiaoa Jun Soo Hyun
Kim Soo-Hyuk
Will not make money
Is a very low-level network cartoonist
You are mistaken
You picked the wrong husband
All shot in the head direct death
Have been a fight
Was fatally injured
I say
If the purpose of the Secretary of kidnapping words
Not necessary to do
This should be an execution
Damn this guy
Deputy general
Jason Lee You remember
That lunatic terrorists
Jason to the Republic of Korea
Park today to find to our editor in chief of intelligence
Its use of violence
what
And this just uploaded
西蒙死亡
Now all the clues was connected
This time we dig agent's eyes and kill them
Jason
Arjun is our intelligence agents gave Jason
No way
You brats
Not yet understand
He is deliberately cartoonist
In order to sneak into our internal
Not that we caught him
He let us caught
How to locate a cell phone
Phone off
Brats
Not that kid is thousands Secretary
Secretary of the phone can not be located in the phone
How do children like children
Arrived
open
Immediately contact the Secretary for one thousand
Open release
Countries have not abandoned you
Forgiveness and hope the road is also open for you
Oh shit, then say it
What the country has given me
What is that sound
what
My phone off ah
Oh this should be the sound of an engine it
The car is too old really quivering
Ouch broken car
It seems not
what is this
You a mobile phone hidden here yet
no mobile phone
Not out
That is not the phone is glow sticks glow sticks
Why do not you feel that there Fluorescent
You relax
There can not be
Do not touch
Can not
One thousand one thousand Secretary Secretary
Minister is
It depends ...
What are you doing
If you want to see your daughter dead, then give me a U-turn
I say
Are you there Daddy Daddy
- Great Britain - Dad
Jia Ying Where are you
It did not hurt
Dad where are you
Jia Ying I love you
If you dared to touch my daughter Yigenhanmao
They all dead brats who
Do not grasp the pain
Damn
Dad where are you
Jia Ying Are you all right
Dad, I'm scared
what should I do
Jia Ying wait for me I'll pick you up
If you want to save your daughter
Immediately came back with one thousand Secretary
The traitor betrayed his colleagues also feel that their children are baby right
If you dared to touch my daughter Yigenhanmao
You really dead
it is good
Damn
崔亨道次長
father
- Daddy save me - What to do
What to do
father
What I have done for this country out
Men who killed my man his daughter's life
I think I would care about it
No
I did not kill anyone
The Spy Kids see you acting
Secretary sent back quickly to one thousand
Otherwise, your daughter died
Please stop
stop
Dad saved me
Pull back
father
Now immediately bring back one thousand Secretary
If you want to save your daughter's words
I will kill everyone
Your husband come
Knowing that he will die also come
Awesome Love
Husband
Her husband not to come
Not to walk walk
Walk walk
Sorry
What ah where are you going
Where to
Why the U-turn
What the fuck
Brats
Damn brats
You still do pup husband
After I got married so hard to live
Asshole
Well I have to die
There is some thing
Do not wait for my wife
Just what is the U-turn
I now want to kill your wife yet
Can not
NIS who kidnapped my daughter
So just turn around
You make me believe it now
It is the guy, right Kim Soo
I told him to change
I swear to my life
Saved my daughter I'll be right there
Please do not hurt my wife
How you make me believe you
I am a traitor to the country to hunt
Been wronged kill
It is your work
Not too late
Otherwise, your wife will die
My poor Mina
He has been in hard
What man cry cry
Would have been no blood no tears to the people
You really changed a lot ah
It's that concerned about it
How can we not worry
My wife now
But a woman full of
Really weak
Damn smelly shameless
Like you son of a bitch is still my husband is crazy
Damn you
You son of a bitch
When I try to go out
You are dead
When I go out
OK OK
- let go - do not move
Do it
The child who is chief
Spy Kids daughter
what
open
Minister of kidnapping a child is not right
what
Arjuna boy killed our agents
Can you say such a thing it
be honest
I do not believe Arjun older generation can do such a thing
Arjuna Arjuna Arjuna damn
One thousand Secretary also you this kid is really ...
Iris is also a shield to defend him you do
She is not a hide like a mobile phone
The ability to turn it
do not move
Do not move this is sexual harassment
I will accuse you
- candid - do not move
Stop me
come
Why did what ah
stop
Turned over nothing
The child said to the Queen
How to do
so troublesome
what happened
You are taking me that my father was right
do not worry
Dad will see the
佳英 爸爸我現在在花津浦區 我從那些叔叔那逃出來了
How suddenly so fast
My daughter is in the vicinity of
You only do I have to wear a seat belt system ...
You put this pull pull
Hurry Hurry pull
Jia Ying father to find you
Mobile is now
Information about Aci pay out
Positioned immediately
Jia Ying
father
Jia Ying all right
Sorry for being late father go
stop
Hey kid to help me untie
Come untie
- Hey Boy Hey - knees Hands
I do not want to shoot in front of your daughter
What are you doing Uncle
father
Let my daughter leave aci
Aci uncle
Aci uncle of my father mentioned it
do you know me
Occasionally my father would say if you drink something
Dad orphans without family
Like there is a younger brother of the same family
But even imagine also see
Not to say the same as the younger brother of relationship do
How can this
You do not know too small
Your father is a spy
Do hard labor at the construction site spy it
You know how daddy do hard labor
Why do not you know my mother knows
- your mother know you - ah
Put your hands up
My father
Do you know how much he poor
Do not wash painting all day, what with diffuse network
Be scolded all day
Make money all day long been ignored mom
Have always been nagging grandparents
There is no way to go home, father
Jia Ying
do not talk
And my father
Jia Ying
Before my mother drunk
Let my father die
And my father
Do not say do not say do not say
Why roar child ah
how come
When the brother how would this brother
You do not think his poor
Then why do you kidnap Secretary
Arjun's wife was kidnapped
He threatened to let him take me past
In short, without discernment you ago
In front of the children what would you say
Mom do
By whom
do not worry
Dad immediately to save mother
Uncle will go together
Uncle and father are legendary kite shield
and many more
Coupled with a man
I'm the original kite shield
I say to untie
come in
Where you have to be seniors, I received
It would have been my place
Here is where the ancient shield to provide a kite
You look at this brother
Still ah
This is the father of it
I would like you to
And I really respect you
Aci uncle
Dad is a fan of
Whoops whoops between a man so sick
How such a large refrigerator
What's cool Sprite ...
You leave this kid a lot of things ah
just in case
To get back the feeling before it
All right
- Let's go - ah
Please wait
fool
- out a - is
I'll convince them
Do you think Cui times long can you listen to your words
Aci first sorry
What sorry
Why hit me
Dad why are you beating
Why beat ah boy
You have to take a beating
Pretending to be a person you want to catch me
The result was I ran
and many more
Sorry
Super pain
So cool
Father and uncle will immediately save the mother out
You go to grandma
Do not
I have to go
I'm going to mom
Listen to the words of my father
This is not child's energy mix
no no
If they get caught uncle how to do that
I'm really scared
I have to go
Then you have to listen to the words of my father
Ok
But Dad
Net Man in the story
All because my father happened to do it
what happened
Are you afraid you dad
No
The thought of network Man hero dad
I felt pity
Young age, was taken away by how hard ah
Dad, you are tired of it
Even so your father at first, but that it
Will still shooting
Serving with gunmen
You know how Uncle
I also comics
really
Who you are inside
The instructors
Ah teacher that taught him
That this is the devil instructor uncle
Why hit me
Why are you so against my father
You see this look
Exactly like your father
Really. ...
Oh no children who are much aggrieved
But where in the backpack
In the rear compartment do
Rear seats do not
Captain your backpack is not back yet
There are all weapons
I back it
I have joined many years the shield kite course you have to come back up
I joined many years
That no weapon Hello
That how fighting
This kid is how it
Do you want to start a war
So you want to convince Arjun let him surrender it
Then was caught here
Yes
I want a person to solve this problem
What kid
Acting alone can never forgive
Let the kid escaped more ...
Let him go
Minister if this kid how to do and unauthorized actions
Who among you have the confidence to win his talk to Arjuna singled
Let me chilling guys
Be sure to catch the guy
Even kill him
Otherwise, death is you
Yes
千德奎局長
Where are you now
Give me
Jia Ying I aci uncle
Your father do
Dad let me give you a call
Doing it fast positioning his position
There you go again not run away yet
Jason madman
It's him
Not you personally tortured Jason's brother
Then brutally killed him yet
Why are you saying these things now ah
You do not put his eyes out yet
You also kidnapped his brother
You make me do that before I do, ah obey orders
I see your comics
My brother painful death
Before I have killed the wrong man
In fact, the two of you are doing
The original killed our agents who are you
Ah They have been begging me to let them
But I have been tortured them
Then they killed
Their eyes are also dug up
You will become like that
Anyway I follow the convention to bring the
Where my wife
Oh
Hurts ah damn drunk really made a big
- Mina - stopped him
Do not hit my husband
Shit
Dog dare you something my husband
Do not touch me touch me ...
You have to take a beating because as a dog right thing
Brat
How your wife is going
What did you do to my wife
I was her own drink expensive wine
She is alcoholism ah
Scold her brats
Are you okay Are you okay
You sober
I do not let you quit drinking yet
Hey you this kid
are you human
Hey How dare you leave me run away to escape
I'm not back yet
I go for a reason
You comic hero is not me.
Are you compile it
Are compiled out of it
Sorry
He do not show you
You do not Kim Soo Hyuk
Jin Fengjun
I am not Kim Soo Hyuk Jin Fengjun
So I was assassinated agents Arjun
Say what Jin Fengjun brats
I'm sorry I lied to you
I'm sorry it would be finished
We are now divorced
Those are things
After I met you I had changed
You TM is a liar Jin Fengjun
So that your past is not the same yet
Now you must pay the price for what you did
What are the costs
The pay is that you ah
You killer
Those of you who kill
Our agents
bring here
stop fighting
Oh, can not so easily to kill him
Thanks
Until you beg me to kill you so far
I will not kill you
Anyway I have kept the agreement
To put my wife caught me
There are things to help you
Hey this is what you are doing
let me go
Damn
He is my brother how to
You how to him
You think you can do nothing
We also track you
You will die in torture in
Damn
You were cultured people killed
How do you
do you need my help
stop
okay, I get it
I come
I do not blame the captain
Arjun You do not really want to do it
How can you do this to me
They are doing it
The movie enlarge
He was tortured one thousand Secretary
Damn guy
I say this kid and they are a group
Do not
Faster then faster
My brother died the same way it
Then came
Wait a minute
you are like
You seem to have a lot of misunderstanding
He painted the cartoon is very exaggerated
I have no exaggeration to draw
You ungrateful man
How can you do this to me
I how to train your
Brats brats brats
You okay
Are you ok
And pressed feed
You also feel the taste of the fire it
do not move
To my wife put you burn it
Determine the target
Will not move
Resistance will be killed
OK OK
- Oh Secretary - Give this to me knocked off
Such a cruel thing
Come on kid doing it
This Haohen
This bite off bite off
To hurry up
All right
I saw you come out of hiding that
I did not kill the agents of
All he did
Worthy of a cartoonist is not an ordinary can really nonsense ah
You and Jason and his gang do not
You're not kidnapped as he said it a thousand Secretary
I have no way
They kidnapped my wife
My husband was right
This guy
Brats kidnapped me
Do you think we are fools
We see you torture the director of one thousand
He let me do
What I said do not you want to do
Are you saying that they want to do, ah
You make me do ah
This ... Shit
First Knock
This guy ...
I saw this guy wanted to kill him
Two of them are a group of
Why this guy wanted to kill him then
But he did not die until now
You so soon forget it
This kid can disguise his own death was watertight
Really going crazy
How many times have I said that I did not kill the damn really speechless
I caught up to him
- Do not come over do not come - do not come
You go
I told you not to come
Yes ah you can not be without a fight
Direct shot and killed him
No No Do not shoot
You put the gun down
I'll persuade him
give me sometime
You are not crazy dare you
Why do you shoot ah
Do not
Can not
What guns open fire
Do not shoot
Arjun predecessors is being wronged
I really want to cry the tears
Change target
The goal is Arjun
Arjun will disappear and disappear along with our dark past
Do not shoot my father
- Great Britain - you go
- Do not shoot my dad - good English
Do not shoot my father
Do not shoot
Woman and child from him too close
Long shot like a traitor for fast shot
How to do
Fast shot
No No
Aci
This kid finally
Why would you do aci
brother
Brother you have family ah
But I have no family
There is no love nothing
I'm just passing through
What passing
This gun is not lethal Azheezhe
Hey kid
Hey Hey brats
Hey brats up ah sober up
Sober sober
This fool say
Fast shot
Hey you give me a shot aimed at the
I was aiming ah
what's the situation
Brat
Good marksmanship
Husband
father
Daddy will not die
Let them put the gun down
- or I'll kill you all - Daddy
Husband
Daddy will not die
Regard the gun down
Put the gun down
Get out the gun down
Brat
Why do kid
Come to me come
father
- I'm sorry my husband - my father how do how to do how to do
- Dad - husband
Daddy
Arjun is dead in the process and you fight in
Because you falsely accused him of being a spy
You fool
I am not saying Arjun not a spy thing brats
Are you talking to me
For what you brats
Come on headphones win battle was over still wearing
Are you mad how dare you speak and Minister
Are you crazy
Secretary to tell the truth to this situation now because he does not do
How can like it anyway, we have to be dead
Oh damn you do not play
You're dead boy
MD you come to me
Minister sorry sorry
Quiet quiet
- You're dead boy - whom you spit it
Are you crazy
- looks like a joke - quiet
I'm sorry that you have a lot of adults
One thousand Secretary You know I hate the following guilty
After you rejoin
I wrote 100 confessions
Repentance
I do not write you dog
I could not even get married because you are not going to die knot
How are you going to do your thing this dog
This dog thing for you
You dogs! Really
Damn
Hey You crazy
Do you know who I am
You come at me the equivalent of Han Guozheng ...
I wanted to kill you in front of him
But I killed him first
do not worry
father
Husband
- I absolutely can not leave the two of you so dead - her husband
Brats
Give me catch them
Damn it hurts
Okay it did not hurt
Daddy I'm fine
Without this my wife died
Wearing two ah
Please put
Really
Jia Ying also wear
Wife
What if I have an accident
You have to take the good of our family raised English
Do not say such a thing
I hide my past really sorry
it's all my fault
I also was wrong
Bully always nagging you every day
I was not wrong
it's all my fault
The captain of my family please you
Ok
My daughter Jia Ying
You are my daughter
Dad really feel very happy
father
You go to hell
What the fuck
Damn
Bring it on Boy
You boy
Pain you
It really hurt boy
I'm the legend of the devil instructor
Devil awesome instructor
Shit
Back on to you
Next ace kite shield
Finally over
My last task kite shield
Mission impossible ...
- Arjun - - Dad
- husband - Arjuna
Really handsome brother
The last mission ends
權相佑
鄭俊浩
黃雨瑟惠 李伊庚
李智媛 許成泰
趙雲 許棟元 李俊赫
該漫畫為個人創作 漫畫裡的機構、人名、商號純屬虛構 完成終極任務！
Feel Feel
The older generation
Russia today there and hack our computer network
Now you want to catch more than one or two predecessors
If such a state, then
You are found just a matter of time
You will help me fight for Some Time
After we went to the family could live peacefully
Can not can not be delayed
Hey, if not my words
You are dead already wiped out
These are not little children sense of obligation
Wait, you say loyalty loyalty
Yes it is loyalty boy
This is really a sense of obligation
Oh I really
Did not even know you're wearing two bulletproof vests also jump into
Then you remember that time
Really is a damn
I'm sorry it pain you
Do not do nothing
Really sick of it
But the older generation not to draw any cartoons
Agents do not intend to return it
I think the Secretary and the Minister also something to look forward
Really funny ah
I shot it was also open
Now suddenly say
Hey tell them that forget it
How I reached this point
I want to draw comics
Oh damn
Cartoons not to say that the monthly income of less than 500 000
You have to attach to the sister-in-law when
Jia Ying in front of you do not feel ashamed
What are you seniors
Parasites do
The lowest-paying jobs than earned it more than 500,000
Do not say
My dad cartoons will be very red
How would you know how ah
I have seen ah
See how you will see what ah ah
I sat to read the time machine
My dad is really popular cartoons
Whoops
it is true
Is really my husband will be very red
Really ah
See it
I believe there are two people here
Do you think I will not do it
OCR from subtitle subtitles video network transmission of the original hard hard captions produced by the group TSKS subtitles
導演一崔元燮